tvnewsroom.org 2016-12-19

# Privacy Policy - Plus!

**Privacy Policy of TV Newsroom (TVNewsroom, TVN, tvnewsroom.co.uk, tvnewsroom.co.uk, tvnewsroom.net)**

At TV Newsroom, we recognise that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit TV Newsroom, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

**Log Files**  
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as BT or SKY etc), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. 

**Cookies**  
We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

**Google Adverts**  
We also use third party advertisements on TV Newsroom to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

You can turn off the use of cookies at anytime by changing your specific browser settings.

This privacy policy is subject to change without notice and was **last updated on January, 15, 2015**. If you have any questions feel free to contact me directly: privacy@tvnewsroom.co.uk.
